thislilpiglet.net 2012-11-30

# Privacy Policy - This Lil Piglet

Privacy Policy – www.thislilpiglet.net

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at stacey@thislilpiglet.net.

At www.thislilpiglet.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.thislilpiglet.net and how it is used.

Other than third party ad uses of cookies and log files detailed below, This Lil Piglet will never sell or share your information with anyone and will not use your information for anything other than it’s intended purpose such as opt in newsletter subscriptions.  Information submitted for giveaways will only be used in the event that you are the winner of the giveaway; in this event your contact information will be forwarded to the sponsoring company for that prize in order for shipment and only your name will or may be announced on the This Lil Piglet website.  At times This Lil Piglet will collect various data from readers of the website intended for the use of determining the demographic reach of readership; any and all attempts will be announced in these instance, will strictly be a generalization and will be your choice if you choose to participate.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.thislilpiglet.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.thislilpiglet.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.thislilpiglet.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.thislilpiglet.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.thislilpiglet.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
